Preliminary Guide to the Frank Bardacke Papers M2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Research Files
  - Subseries 4.6: Clippings; Miscellaneous Publications; Print Materials; etc.
    - Destablization Campaign Oanz, 26 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Rubio Memo, 26 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Mojica: Dolores and Jews, 26 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Ortiz letter to Cesar on Jews, 26 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Grossman, 1,000 Mile March, 26 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Judios/"El Plan" de Marshall, 26 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Cesar Jenny 9/5/80 - 11/13/80, 26 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - UFW - [Dunne], 26 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Dispute At Coachella Field office 1971-72, 26 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Prologue Notes, 26 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Man Freeman, 26 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - UFW Booknotes, 26 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - 1968 Vote in Coachella see [H...], 26 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Cursillos, 26 (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - Trotsky on Trade Unions, 26 (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - Mother Jones/CIR/Manuel Chavez, 26 (Box 52, Folder 44)
    - Arizona Farmworkers, 26 (Box 52, Folder 45)
    - Yuma 1974, 75, 77, 26 (Box 52, Folder 46)
    - Baldemar to Antonio 1979, 26 (Box 52, Folder 47)
    - Maturino Files, 26 (Box 52, Folder 48)
    - Camacho's Threat, 26 (Box 52, Folder 49)
    - Ronald Taylor Chavez Farmworker, 26 (Box 52, Folder 50)
    - Chavez Day [Watsonville], 26 (Box 52, Folder 51)
    - Bruce Church 1996 Contract, 26 (Box 52, Folder 52)
    - Chavez Obits, 26 (Box 52, Folder 53)
    - Letter to Joann, 26 (Box 52, Folder 54)
    - Nepotism in US Labor, 26 (Box 52, Folder 55)
    - His Back, 26 (Box 52, Folder 56)
    - Copland: UFW, 26 (Box 52, Folder 57)
    - Krissman PHD Thesis, 26 (Box 52, Folder 58)
    - FLOC, 26 (Box 52, Folder 59)
    - Manuel Chavez Missing Checks, 27 (Box 52, Folder 60)
    - AFW Interviews, 27 (Box 52, Folder 61)
    - Pete Maturino Files, 27 (Box 52, Folder 62)
    - Castle and Cooke in Nicaragua, 27 (Box 52, Folder 63)
    - La BOTZ Immigration #s, 27 (Box 52, Folder 64)
    - Menlo College/Dolores, 27 (Box 52, Folder 65)
    - Virginia Hirsch, 27 (Box 52, Folder 66)
    - Fred Hirsch, 27 (Box 52, Folder 67)
    - LHM, 27 (Box 52, Folder 68)
    - Carmen Hernandez, 27 (Box 52, Folder 69)
    - Angie Herrera and Carmen Hernandez, 27 (Box 52, Folder 70)
    - Helen Hernandez, 27 (Box 52, Folder 71)
    - Julio Hernandez CSN, 27 (Box 52, Folder 72)
    - Henggeler, 27 (Box 52, Folder 73)
    - Dona Haber, 27 (Box 52, Folder 74)
    - [Cortez Guzman], 27 (Box 52, Folder 75)
    - Gus Guttierrez, 27 (Box 52, Folder 76)
    - Jessica Govea, 27 (Box 52, Folder 77)
    - Nick Jones Res., 27 (Box 52, Folder 78)
    - Nick Jones, 27 (Box 52, Folder 79)
    - Various News clippings, 22 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Various News clippings, 22 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Various News clippings, 22 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - My Analysis of Agribusiness for The Collective Circa 1975 - 1976, 22 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Me Llamo Marco [Marc Sapir draft memoir] (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 4.7: Henggeler Manuscript [unpublished]
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (1 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (2 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (3 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (4 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (5 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (6 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Henggler (7 of 7), 19 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 4.8: Freedom of Information Act Files
    - Freedom of Info Act FB 1 File, 21 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Robert and Joseph Digiorgio, 21 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Blum, Grape Govers, 21 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Harvest of Shame, 21 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - State Senate Debo Hearing 1966, 21 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Grower Anti-Union 1960s, 21 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - SNCC! Klein, 21 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Bob Moses, 21 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - AG Stats 1960-65, 21 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Conference at SF State [Labor City], 21 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Seed to Superintendent, 21 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Is (Entry) on Grapes, 21 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ann Draper and Krebs, 21 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - John Gregory Dunne article 1967, 21 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Fitzsimmon, Margaret, 21 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Untitled Folder, 21 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Ben-Amotz, 21 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Glass and Camney, 21 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Tomlins, C. NLRB History, 21 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Kirkdon, 21 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Amanda Gamble, 21 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - UFW Constitution, 21 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Sweet on Wage Rates, 21 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - 1961 Salinas Calif. STMTN Strike, 21 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Anti-Oraegro 1961 Campaign, 21 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Dunne, 21 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Longtime Coming Metster/Lofts, 21 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Kushner, 21 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Healy Remember, 21 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Navarro, "Economic Effects of [immigration] on Mexico", 21 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Stein Oakies, 21 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Logan, Wayne Act, 21 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - National State, 21 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - David Igler/ Haggin, 21 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Ron Davis, 21 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Cesar to Senate Committee '66, 21 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Calavita Inside the State, 21 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - "America" Thurston Davis 1966 Pilgrimage, 21 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Teri Esparza, 21 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Gitlin, 21 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Braverman/Aronowitz, 21 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Edmund Wilson: [Amerkian] EQ, 21 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Jane Brown's Am. To Grower Clove 1968, 21 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Letters and Grant Leads, 21 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Biblio Questions, 21 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Schmidt, Jeffrey, 21 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Dana Drinkwater, 21 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Mango McBane, 21 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Rain of Good, 21 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Foster Beach Proposal, 21 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Holfman Connected Amer., 21 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Mitchell, The Lie of the Land, 21 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Ryan, Higgins, Seaton, 21 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Braverman, 21 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Water/George Goldman, 21 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Thower, Maps w/ Mar, 21 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Limoneira Paper, 21 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Kopkind '65 Strike, 21 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Glenna Mathews "Women of the Boycott, 21 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Glabs: Poverty: The Valley of Plenty, 21 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Digiorgio 1966-67 Loaplets, 21 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Hijo de Hartmire, 21 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Chris Hartmire, 21 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Hartmire Essays, 21 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Hartmire: "Internal Revolution", 21 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Hartmire, 21 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Subseries 4.9: Miscellaneous Material
    - Various CDs [Bob Fitch photgraphs], 12 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 12 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 12 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Mario Photo, 12 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, 12 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Photos Imperial Valley, 12 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 12 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - timelines, etc., 12 (Othertype 36)
  - Subseries 4.10: Biographical Files; Subject Files
    - Dolores Huerta, 27 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Dolores Huerta, 27 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Juan Huerta/Watson, 27 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Ray Huerta, 27 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Richard Garcia on Dolores Huerta, 27 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Mutan, 27 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Larry Itliong, 27 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Bill Kircher/Watson, 27 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Kircher on 1973 Negotiations, 27 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Carold Lambiase, 27 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Bleechie Levitt, 27 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Marsha Eliebracht, 27 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Jack Lloyd, 27 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - John Logan ALRB, 27 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Draft Dodging, 27 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Ben Maddock, 27 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Luis Magana, 27 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Pete Maturino, 27 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Father McDonnell, 27 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Eliseo Medina, 27 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Richard Mines and Citrus Notes, 27 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Mojica, 27 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Bill Monning, 27 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Oscar Mondragon Doc Project, 27 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Tirso Moreno, 27 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Marion Moses, 27 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Crecencio Diaz, 27 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Mike Dobler, 27 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Jim Brake, 27 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Alecia Matsuoka Susan Drake, 27 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Jose Dzib/Watson, 27 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Pablo Espinoza CSN, 27 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Esher, 27 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Pablo Espinoza, 27 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Fishlow, 27 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Bob Fitch, 27 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Juan Flores, 27 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Eddie Frankel, 27 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Eddie Frankel, 27 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Galanza Talk 1974, 27 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Robert Garcia/Watson, 27 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Paid Reps: Early Years, 27 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Chavarria, Lenin, 27 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Sam Cohen, 27 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Jerry Cohen, 27 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Jerry Cohen, 27 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Jerry Cohen in Jerry and Fact, 27 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Manuel Chavez, 27 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Jerry Cohen /AKA Lance Laconic, 27 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Tom Dalzell, 27 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - RG Davis, 27 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Jessie de La Cruz, 27 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - Mark Day, 27 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Chava Bustamonte, 27 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Chap 1 Interviews, 27 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Epifamio Camacho, 27 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Bill Chandler CSN, 27 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - Terry Cannon, 27 (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - Leroy Chatfield, 27 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Leroy Chatfield, 27 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - Chatfield, 27 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Fred Abad, 27 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - Alfredo Avila, 27 (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - George Ballis, 27 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - Bertha Batres, 27 (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Lyle Berg/Watson, 27 (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - Carlos Bowker, 27 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - Braulio, 27 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - John Brown, 27 (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - John Brown, 27 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - John Brown, 27 (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - Burciaga, 27 (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - Memories of El Centro Sept. 05, La Paz Tapes (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - Gretchen Law (Bustamonte), La Paz Tapes (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - Mario Bustamonte - Interview, La Paz Tapes (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Tribute to Jessica Govea Thorbourne, La Paz Tapes (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Eliseo Medina, La Paz Tapes (Box 53, Folder 77)
- Series 5: Media
  Scope and Contents
  Many of the recordings are interviews by Bardacke in preparation for his books. There are also proceedings from UFW meetings.
  - Marshall [Ganz] 1, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 1)
  - Marshall [Ganz] 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 2)
  - Marshall [Ganz] 3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 3)
  - Marshall [Ganz] 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 4)
  - Marshall [Ganz] 5, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 5)
  - Marshall [Ganz] 6, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 6)
  - Eliseo [Medina] 1 May 20, 2005, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 7)
  - Eliseo [Medina] 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 8)
  - Beatles Greatest Hits. Quien Sabe?, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 9)
  - Bob Pepper 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 10)
  - Bob Pepper 3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 11)
  - [Gilbert and/or Esther] Padilla and [Hermilo] Mojica 12/21/97 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 12)
  - [Gilbert and/or Esther] Padilla and [Hermilo] Mojica 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 13)
  - [Gilbert and/or Esther] Padilla and [Hermilo] Mojica 5, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 14)
  - Maggie and Camera 1999, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 15)
  - Hank Anderson, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 16)
  - Father Greg Boyle 2/10/96, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 17)
  - Mario [Bustamente] Memorial Day 2006 #1, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 18)
  - Mario [Bustamente] Memorial Day 2006 #2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 19)
  - Mario [Bustamente] Memorial Day 2006 #3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 20)
  - Mario [Bustamente] Memorial Day 2006 #4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 21)
  - Al Rojas I, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 37, Audiocassette 22)
  - Al Rojas II, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 1)
  - [Al] Rojas III Jan 27, 2003 side 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 2)
  - [Amber? Austen?] Aug 05 Tape 1, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 3)
  - [Amber? Austen?] Tape 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 4)
  - [Amber? Austen?] Tape 3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 5)
  - Pablo [Espinoza] Telephone 2/9/04, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 6)
  - Pablo [Espinoza] Side 1 and 2 Feb. 6, 2000, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 7)
  - Pablo [Espinoza] Side 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 8)
  - Pablo [Espinoza] 5 and 6, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 9)
  - [Doug and/or Debbie] Adair #1, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 10)
  - [Doug and/or Debbie] Adair #2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 11)
  - [Doug and/or Debbie] Adair #4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 12)
  - [Doug and/or Debbie] Adair #5, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 13)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica Jul. 02, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 14)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica Nov. 06, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 15)
  - Fred Hirsch Santa Cruz 3 and Maybe 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 16)
  - Fred Hirsch Oct 3 [1997] 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 17)
  - Gus [Gustavo] Gutierrez 3/04, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 18)
  - [Hartmire?] December 1997 December 6, 1997, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 19)
  - Jessica Govea 11/18/02, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 20)
  - Jessica Govea 12/6/02 I, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 21)
  - Jessica Govea 12/6/02 II, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 22)
  - Jessica Govea 12/6/02 III, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 38, Audiocassette 23)
  - Berta [Batres] Nov. 29, 06, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 1)
  - Mark Day 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 2)
  - Jose Renteria Side 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 3)
  - Jose Renteria Side 3 and a little 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 4)
  - Radio Show Review of [Lofts?] book, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 5)
  - Luis Magana Side I and II 2/5/08, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 6)
  - Luis Magana Tape 2 Feb 5, 2008, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 7)
  - Ventura [Gutierrez?], My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 8)
  - Sam Koshane KPFK; Convention 1981 With Doug Adair, Mark Day, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 9)
  - Albert Rojas Side one and Side two, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 10)
  - Albert Rojas Side 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 11)
  - Pato [Doug Adair] April 29, 2005, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 12)
  - Pato [Doug Adair] 4/29/05, Side two 4/30/05, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 13)
  - Adair #3 Doug Adair 3/23/95 Carlos, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 14)
  - Epifanio Camacho Sides 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 15)
  - Epifanio Camacho 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 16)
  - Epifanio Camacho 5 and 6, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 17)
  - Nick Jones March 21 2002, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 18)
  - Jerry Cohen Side one and two, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 19)
  - Jerry Cohen Side 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 20)
  - Jerry Cohen side 5, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 21)
  - Jerry Cohen follow up interview Not Transcribed July 14, 1965, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 39, Audiocassette 22)
  - Jessica Govea Nov. 12 Nov. 27 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 1)
  - Jessica [Govea] March 1, 2002; March 28, 2002 #3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 2)
  - Jessica [Govea] March 28, 2002 #5, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 3)
  - [Chaur?] 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 4)
  - [Chaur?] 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 5)
  - Ben Maddock May 1, 2005, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 6)
  - Gretchen Lau + Mario [Bustamente?] April 29, 2005; Ben Maddock May 1, 2005, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 7)
  - Pato [Doug Adair] June 15 Side 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 8)
  - Pato [Doug Adair] 6/15 Side 3; Chayo [Pelayo] 6/15 Side 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 9)
  - Chayo [Pelayo] 6/15 2 and 3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 10)
  - Carol L 1, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 11)
  - Carol L 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 12)
  - John Soria 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 13)
  - John Soria 3 and 4, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 14)
  - John Soria 5 and 6, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 15)
  - John Soria 7 and 8, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 16)
  - John Soria 9 and 10, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 17)
  - Ginny Hirsch October 6, 1997 Side 1 and 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 18)
  - Ginny Hirsch Side 3 October 6, 1997, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 19)
  - [Epifanio or Pablo] Camacho, [Hermilo] Mojica, [Mario or Salvador] Bustamente and [Al] Rojas Jan 27, 2003, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 20)
  - Radio Program on Watsonville, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 21)
  - Mario [Bustamente] and Chayo [Pelayo] April 30, 2005 Tape 1, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 22)
  - Mario [Bustamente] and Chayo [Pelayo] Tape 2, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 23)
  - End of Mario [Bustamente] and Chayo [Pelayo]; Beginning of Gretchen Lau; Gretchen 3, My Tapes; audiocassette (Box 40, Audiocassette 24)
  - Mario Bustamente I, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 1)
  - Mario Bustamente II, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 2)
  - Mario Bustamente III twenty minutes missing, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 3)
  - Mario Bustamente IV, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 4)
  - Mario Bustamente V, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 5)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica II Side 1 and 2 Oct. 24, 1994, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 6)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica II Side 3 and 4 Oct. 24, 1994, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 7)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica I Oct. 3, 1994 Side 3 and Side 4, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 8)
  - More [Hermilo] Mojica, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 9)
  - [Mami I] Feb. 1, 1995, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 10)
  - Carnalito 3/16/95, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 11)
  - Mike Dobler Jan 20, 1995, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 12)
  - [Doug and/or Debbie] Adair 1, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 13)
  - [Doug and/or Debbie] Adair 2 May, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 14)
  - Debbie [Adair] 1 May 11 [post-it "Mojica I Oct.3 12"], My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 15)
  - Doug, Debbie [Adair] 2, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 16)
  - Berta [Batres] I, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 17)
  - Berta [Batres] II Oct 3, 1994 Side #1, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 18)
  - Aristeo [Zambrano] I, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 19)
  - Aristeo [Zambrano] II, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 20)
  - Pablo [Camacho] I 1/20/95, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 21)
  - Pablo [Camacho] IA 1/20/95, My Tapes; microcassette (Box 41, Audiocassette 22)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library Bardacke 2011-1469 (1 of 2), My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 23)
  - Frank 3/11, My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 25)
  - Mom's Doll, My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 26)
  - Stop at 7452 13th Now, My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 27)
  - [unlabeled CDR, possibly blank], My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 28)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library Bardacke 2011-1469 (2 of 2), My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 29)
  - [unlabeled CDR, possibly blank], My Tapes; CD-R (Box 41, Disk 30)
  - Carlos, My Tapes; computer diskette (Box 41, Disk 31)
  - Executive Board 8/25/77 Fresno, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 1)
  - Synanon, 2/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 2)
  - Crosby Milne 9/11/76, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 3)
  - UFW AFL CIO National Executive Board Meeting, Tape #16, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 4)
  - UFW National Executive Board Meeting - United Farm Workers March 29, 1974 reel 13, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 5)
  - UFW National Executive Board Meeting Friday March 29th 1974, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 6)
  - Lamont Strike, Giumarra 8/10/73, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 7)
  - Lamont 8/13/73 Strikers released 8/15 Pete Juares Delano Picket, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 8)
  - Delano Open Air Meeting 8/17/93, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 9)
  - Delano Open Air Meeting 8/17/73 I, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 10)
  - Dolores Huerta, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 11)
  - Robert Garcia, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 12)
  - Cesar Chavez, December 30, 1972, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 13)
  - Synanon Game at La Paz Tape #3 5/3/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 14)
  - UFW Reunion 11/11/01, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 15)
  - UFW Executive Board 12/5-7/77 Tape 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 16)
  - UFW Reunion 11/11/01 tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 17)
  - UFW Reunion 11/11/01 tape 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 18)
  - Phillip Vera Cruz 1979, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 19)
  - Phil Vera Cruz 1979. Part 1, Delano 4/19/78. Margo McBane, Mary Winegarden, RT, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 20)
  - Phil Vera Cruz 1979. Part II August 10, 1979. Phillip Vera Cruz, Delano With Mary Winegarden, Margo McBane, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 21)
  - Phil Vera Cruz 1979 Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 22)